Is there joking aside any mild
disappointment? [music] Like this is the
cool this is the annual meeting like the
photos kind of a big deal.
>> No, there's major disappointments. So I
went and got a haircut for God's sake.
Wouldn't have gotten the haircut if it
wasn't that damn important, but [music]
I went I went and got the haircut and
then missed it.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls,
we're inside of a month to go before the
NFL draft, the 2026 edition. And this is
an on the road edition, an annual
meeting, an owners meeting
edition as some call it, live from the
Biltmore in Arizona. Although we're not
really live cuz Jason Gibbs, hello
Gibby, by the time the best podcast
available presented by Bullseye Event
Group for award-winning gameday
experiences visit
bullseyeeventgroup.com.
By the time this posts we won't be live.
I don't know why I say live. That is
like such a corny like fake newscaster
where I'm like reporting live
shtick.
>> like a Tom Brokaw. I like that.
>> Yeah. All right, buddy. Well, yeah, cuz
my phone is just I keep getting one
weather alert after another. I guess the
end of the world might be coming while
we're taping this podcast.
>> Seriously?
>> So like if the building gets taken out,
like you'll have this podcast to
remember me.
>> Okay, well, there is kin there's kinship
with you
back at the CrossCountry Mortgage campus
here in Arizona. There was a brief
sprinkle.
It's all right around right around noon
today.
Like there there was there was moisture
falling from the sky. The people were
frightened.
What is this? I don't know what this is.
I I don't know. I don't know. I'm so
confused.
>> I don't know. I am jealous that you're
at the Biltmore at uh
I we got to stay there in 2019 and it
was pretty awesome. Was that a win over
the Cardinals in 2019, remind me?
We were done after the first Kyler
Murray
>> Which game was that? I don't remember.
>> Oh.
>> Kneels
>> came off
quick. The good news was we got an extra
day out in the desert. There you go.
Some it was either late November, early
December
uh
we were there. Wasting away in
Zaguraville.
At [laughter] thriving.
Thriving. I remember it was the holiday
season [cough] because
we stumbled [snorts] upon a
a Christmas pop-up bar.
>> Ooh. And it was a warehouse that you had
we had no idea and like there was a
certain knock
and like a certain password and then you
came in and literally it was a football
field long party. Amazing. Amazing. I I
have not had a chance to see that. It's
a first world problem that we've for the
most part been confined to the hotel.
That's how this thing goes. Um the
annual meeting is a really cool event. I
know we talked about it a lot on CBD.
This is where all the coaches can get
together and raise a glass and talk
about things that affect all of their
lives. This is where all the owners can
do the same where all the civic and
others of coaches and owners and GMs and
team presidents and the like can get
together. A family event. There's a big
party on Monday night. Kids are invited.
It is a very cool thing, but it is also
a time where you get to sit down with
the coach and the GM for each of these
teams. Browns obviously are focus here
and and really unpack free agency and
look ahead to the draft and go big
picture planning stuff. Andrew Berry
obviously did not slam the door on
trading Myles Garrett when he met with
the media on Sunday. However, after
speaking with Jimmy and Dee Haslam on
Monday, they were Jimmy was a bit more
firm with that and I in no way am
expecting a Myles Garrett trade. Did we
emphatically hear never never never? No,
but I'm telling you I do not in any way
get that impression. So let's let's
let's move that aside. The Browns
proposal to trade draft picks beyond
three years. I'll
I'll tell you right now there plenty of
people that think it's a good idea.
There are plenty of people that go hey,
this is a cool progressive idea. The NBA
does seven, we do three, who cares?
Let's do five. Who's it hurting? Like
any owner that would vote against it,
friendly reminder,
you have the ability to tell your
general manager or coach don't do the
deal.
That's right.
>> if if somebody else wants to throw his
franchise away or burn the house down
figuratively speaking, it only betters
you. Like what does it matter? Let them
trade away the farm. You still own your
farm, but hey, they withdrew the
proposal because that's how it works.
You don't put stuff to vote unless
you're generally going to get the vote.
So that's the league business. We can
talk about replaying flags and all that
a little bit later.
>> Maxx Crosby and the Ravens saying it was
a slow media
cycle and that's why
>> Yeah, that's not the case. That is not
the case. Listen, I spoke to one team
while we're here and they told a story
about a trade that of recent vintage,
let's put it that way, that they nixed
upon receiving medicals electronically
shared information. It happens. I I know
certainly and the A.J. Epenesa instance,
the Browns it was reported had A.J.
Epenesa they've agreed to terms. The
former Bill is going to sign. They were
not comfortable reportedly with the
physical. That was after A.J. came to
Cleveland. So like it both can be true.
What can be done as we kind of get off
script here to change that? I don't know
that anything can be done. I I really
don't. It's you just hope that the other
guy you're dealing with gives you a fair
shake.
Yeah. I I look, every team has their own
medical team.
It's done. It's buried. We move forward.
There was a lot of news coming out. It's
always good this time of year cuz
[clears throat] you get to hear from the
GM.
You get to hear from the coach
right after your first wave of free
agency. It's the first time that we've
gotten to hear from either one of uh
Andrew Berry or Todd Monken.
Uh and then you get to hear from the
Haslams. And you only really I mean
Jimmy and Dee talk at this event and
they talk at training camp. Yeah. Maybe
a couple other select things, but
otherwise uh
you can learn a lot here in the 48 hours
that you're in Arizona. Let's get let's
get to that cuz I've been sidetracked
here already. You mentioned Maxx Crosby,
man. I went down that road. You we just
killed 2 minutes, dude. All right, let's
talk about the quarterbacks. Deshaun
Watson, Shedeur Sanders, Dillon Gabriel
are all going to get a fair shot at the
quarterback job. They said it at the
combine. I think a lot of people would
no, you don't really mean that, do you?
No, they really do. They really do mean
that. We have a calendar set now on
April 7th because the Browns are one of
the 10 teams with a new head coach. That
is when the offseason program will
begin. No players on the grass. There's
no football stuff. Go out there, work
out, whatever, but it's primarily
meetings. And we should mention Andrew,
learn to be a broadcaster. Todd Monken
will join us coming up shortly. Our
exclusive one-on-one with the new head
coach of your Cleveland Browns. What
will he tell the team? I don't know. He
doesn't have the big speech written yet,
but this is the first chance for him to
say this is what our vision is. And the
vision is competition when it comes to
every position, but specifically the
quarterback position. I'm telling you
Deshaun Watson has a chance. I'm also
telling you that if you want to infer
from Monken speaking today, maybe just
maybe Shedeur Sanders might have that
first shot at the job because Monken
said the way the season ended you might
look at that. Shedeur had job when the
season ended. However, however, just
because one of the quarterbacks is the
frontrunner heading into training camp
the third week of July doesn't mean that
quarterback is handed the job. You got
to go out there and win the job.
Yeah, and it sounds like uh
maybe unlike in years past we'll we'll
have a depth chart when we go to
training camp. We'll have an idea of
reps and who's going to get what. Uh
I I thought it was interesting. Uh I'm
going through my notes here.
Uh love to come out of the spring with a
depth chart. That doesn't mean there's
still not competition, but you have to
narrow the reps or at least balance up
the reps of who you anticipate will come
out of the spring certainly in a
position to be the starter. So clearly
there's a plan in place where it it's
not going to be even reps. It's other
guys are going to have to make up ground
if they want to take over whoever is
going to be the leader in the clubhouse
going into this. And I think Monken's
point that we need to remember is he
said competition is not only on the
field cuz there's limited reps. There's
going to be a voluntary mini camp the
week of the draft. That is news here. We
could tell you that.
But that's voluntary. Again, it's not
like the middle of June where that's the
last thing before training camp here.
You can get a leg up in the classroom
and in areas other than on the field.
And he would like an idea of who that
person could be before we get to
training camp. But the once they get to
training camp, if if the other guy or
one of the other two guys goes out there
and outperforms the guy that's the
presumed starter at the end of the
summer, then that guy gets the job. He
also said we're going to see probably
more of the starters
than we're accustomed to seeing. That
that wasn't the exact way he said it in
the preseason, but that he is going to
play our regulars in the preseason. So
that is notable. As to who's going to
play where, he says they'd prefer Elton
Jenkins he would at guard as opposed to
center, which leads you to believe that
Luke Wypler could be coming off knee
surgery your center, a knee injury, I
beg your pardon. Um
and it leaves unanswered the Joel
Bitonio question. There is no answer yet
on the Joel Bitonio question, but I
think if you follow the tea leaves
without getting out ahead of anything,
you you signed three interior old
lineman in free agency including Teven
Jenkins.
Yeah. I mean no white smoke yet. We
don't we
we don't know what's going on
but I mean this team continues to move
forward and
I thought Todd stuff on Elton Jenkins
was really good. He's hoping to have
Dewan Jones and Luke Whipler back by the
time they finish up the
off season program. I think that's music
to a lot of people's ears.
I think you're going to be pleasantly
surprised when you see Dewan Jones. He
has cut a lot of weight. He has. He's
lean. He looks fast. He's he's putting
in a lot of work right now in the off
season. He's been here every single day.
How do I know? I walk in the building
with him every day. Yeah, and I saw him
I saw him at the combine in Indianapolis
and I got the same impression as well.
He was at that everyone was asked is
Dewan Jones a right tackle or your left
tackle because we remember he started
the season at left tackle but the game
in which he was injured against the
Packers he had actually moved back to
right tackle. Monken made the point
today that he thinks if you're a great
player you could play either side. Not
specifically about Dewan but the
question was more about the tackles in
this draft because this is more of a
right tackle draft than a left tackle
draft and he said hey listen if if
you're great you should be able to play
both.
Yeah.
It will be fascinating to see. I don't
know where I I mean I'm not I'm not the
head coach and I'm not a coach.
I just feel like if you're being signed
to your
and you're a guard I'm hoping that
you're going to play guard
because that's your that's your position
of strength.
I think the tackle situation is
interesting to watch because
we've seen people adapt pretty easily at
making a right tackle to left tackle or
vice versa jump. We've also seen some
guys struggle with that.
We have and I'm I'm bullish on Luke
Whipler.
I love Luke. It's good to have depth and
good to have options. I think we have
fixated so much on who the starting five
is
this off season knowing you need 10 to
11. It's not about the starting five.
The depth has been tested on this O line
and many O lines around the league
constantly the last couple of years.
Consistency and depth for me is the most
important thing. Go back to Sunday. Go
ahead. No no that's you know to to play
off of that. I mean
you don't go no one's trading even
average offensive lineman
during the season. Mhm. Like everybody
holds on to their offensive lineman. So
>> Yeah. you've got to get them now. You've
got to get them via trade before things
start. Once you have your guys in place
it's very hard to go get guys. Yeah, are
there guys on the waiver wire? Sure and
maybe one or two of them work out. We've
seen it happen but
it's tough to get acclimated and get
them
intertwined into the into the Monken
process. I'm going back here Gibby and
I'm looking at my notes from Andrew
Berry on Sunday and he made the point
and I haven't cross checked this but you
know he was spitballing as to the exact
number but he said 23 or 24 teams played
less than 50 or got less than 50%
of their snaps on the
on the O line last year from their
starting five including the Browns. So I
mean three quarters of the league got
less than 50% starting snaps from what
they view as their starting five You
need depth on the O line. You need depth
on the D line and frankly you need depth
at corner. Those are my those are the
big positions. So let's talk about that
because on Sunday Andrew Berry was asked
like why no MJ Emerson back and he he he
was diplomatic with his answer as as he
always was. I got the impression that
MJ would like starter money. They have
two starters in Denzel Ward and in Tyson
Campbell.
And those guys are your starters. He's
coming off MJ is and I want it I would
love to see MJ come back coming off a
legitimate serious injury in training
camp. Obviously it will be exactly one
year when we get to training camp from
that Achilles injury. It's a tough
injury to come back as a corner from.
Obviously there's
there's plenty of opportunity to do it.
Plenty of guys have done it but I I got
the impression well what's the number if
you're not going to be
our number one or our number two corner.
MJ traditionally hasn't played inside.
Right now Miles Harden's playing inside.
You need depth but where do you put him
at at what price? Is there a number that
can make everyone happy? Perhaps but I
think MJ has earned the right to see if
there is a starting job out there. I
don't know about the starting salary out
there at this point on the calendar but
you know I hope he can find it. Maybe
the door is still open.
I I never say never until he signs
somewhere else. Yeah, of course.
>> I'm hoping I'm hoping they can get him
back and
I think again it's just it's depth and
you've got to have depth at the corner
position especially on the outside. You
can figure out the nickel. It's tough to
replace a nickel but if Denzel goes down
and we've seen Denzel go down and miss
some time
last year Tyson Campbell played really
well probably at a pro bowl level if not
maybe some all pro consideration that
should have been given to the young man.
And
but he made it through but it's a long
season and you need depth at outside
corner and frankly inside corners. Yeah,
absolutely. Real quick before we get to
Todd Monken I want to go through my
notes
as as
as quickly and efficiently as I can from
owners Jimmy and Dee Haslam speaking on
Monday.
Jimmy Haslam started by saying basically
I feel the fans pain. It's not fun to
watch. The last two years have not been
acceptable. Got to be better and they
believe that Todd Monken can be the guy.
He's direct. You have no question where
he stands with anyone. He's put together
a very good staff.
Jimmy Haslam said he thinks that Monken
is maybe starting in a in a position
that's better than than many first year
head coaches because of the fact that
the defensive staff has been held over
the majority of it obviously and that
everyone really likes his offensive
staff that he has brought in. Many of
these guys have been Baltimore guys as
well. Jimmy Haslam said that Deshaun is
going to get a fresh start with an
offensive mind at quarterback and
hopefully he has a great chance to get
back to form and that Deshaun with only
19 games over the length of his contract
as a Brown is not for lack of effort. He
has been ravaged by injuries. As for
Miles Garrett Jimmy Haslam said Miles
has been quote an integral part of the
Cleveland Browns and as I said earlier I
did not get any impression at all at all
that he would like to see Miles Garrett
traded. Miles is going to be here.
Yeah, he's not I mean EB was pretty
adamant about it on Sunday and and Jimmy
Haslam and Dee Haslam followed up on
Monday and
basically echoed those statements.
Now let's get Gibby to the most
important conversation here
at the annual meeting and that is
what a handsome haircut Todd Monken has.
It's the best podcast available with the
best coach available right here. First
time I get to interview Todd Monken so
I'm excited for that and I'm going to
start with something here that may sound
awkward but roll with me.
That's a good looking haircut.
Fantastic haircut. Fortunately led to
led me to miss the head coach's picture
but that does look pretty good.
>> So let's explain that. The head coach's
picture was scheduled for noon high
noon. We all saw it on the agenda the
handout the schedule noon on Monday so
you decided was it your decision? My
decision.
>> the haircut. You want to look good for
the picture. 100%.
>> And then
they moved the they moved the picture
up. So I guess that's the price of
missing a meeting.
Where most everybody was in the meeting
but me. So
but I did get a nice haircut out of it.
>> You walked out of there and then you ran
into somebody and I was ready to go. I
was like don't we have to go to the
picture and they said no we just took it
20 minutes ago. So all right so You're
not the only one. Sean McVay missed it
as well.
>> No it worked out well that there were a
couple of us. Is there joking aside any
mild disappointment? Like this is the
cool this is the annual meeting. Like
the photo's kind of a big deal.
>> No there's major disappointments why I
went and got a haircut for God's
[laughter] sake. Wouldn't have gotten
the haircut if it wasn't that damn
important but I went I went and got the
haircut and then missed it. What were
you going to wear? Did you have like the
outfit picked out as well? I had the
right outfit on. I had the outfit on and
the haircut. Just
but it is 2026. I ought to be able to
somehow find a way to
put me in that picture. I think that's
>> There there was there was an AI thing I
think we spent an hour and a half on AI.
I mean for God's sake how cool it is and
how forward thinking it is. Why why
can't they just put my picture in there?
Well good looking haircut aside what has
this experience been like? The you're
part of the fraternity. There there is a
fraternity element certainly to this
event among the coaches plus all the
meetings and the rule changes and all
that. How's the whole thing gone? No
it's been great. No it's pretty cool
pretty surreal after all the years of
working to get to this point then you
know be a part of that fraternity has
been been awesome. April 7th cuz you're
one of the 10 new head coaches you get
to get your team in the building to
start the off season program early.
Again no football stuff yet just
getting your feet wet introducing
yourself to your team. What's that
message going to be like? No it's
exciting. It's it's everything you do is
to be with the players and then
eventually get on the grass with them
and our message is it starts April 7th.
It's really that simple.
Have
>> really else to say other than we start
April 7th and um
I don't There's no speech you've had
like prepared I don't There'll be one
prepared. I don't have it right now, but
we'll we'll be ready come April 7th.
>> How are you? What is this pre-draft
process been like for you? It's been
great. You know, once we got done
putting the staff together, uh we're
doing football in the mornings and then
the afternoons guys are working on, you
know, once free agency got over we've
been working on the draft and once we
get back uh Monday
uh well, actually as as a staff we'll be
back Wednesday, but we'll get back uh
with Andrew in the draft and his people
come Monday. Have you had those aha
moments maybe where you're looking at a
guy in the office and you're going, "You
know what? I'm going to walk down the
hall and I'm going to maybe not pound
the table yet. It's still a month out,
but have you had those moments where
you're like, "You know what? This guy."
Sure. I I I think it goes both ways. I
think there's
when you watch a player
there's aha moments where you're like,
"I really like this player's skill set,
how he fits us." And I think there's
others that like maybe not so much. I
think it works both ways.
But we only have one perspective of that
process, which is watching game tape.
Sure, we make some phone calls and talk
to, you know, coaches or college
coaches, but ultimately it's up to
Andrew and and his staff
uh to make the ultimate call. I I want
to go a little bit deeper on that cuz
you said that at at the breakfast this
morning. You said that game tape is
probably your most important factor
here. I I've heard from coaches over the
years that when you meet with a player,
certainly it's important, right? Do I
like this guy? Do I jive with this guy?
Do I want this guy in my building? But
that the tape really tells the story for
you. I think it's the tape and having
people that you really trust that know
the prospect the best.
And how does your somewhat recent
college experience help you?
>> It helps. I think it's a piece of it.
Just like all of your scouts that that
get out and about. Just like when you're
in college, if you go to high schools
recruiting players, I think it's
important to build relationships, so you
get the right information. Cuz
ultimately whether it's a 20-minute
meeting a 30-minute meeting, an hour
meeting a day with a player
that's nothing compared to a coach or an
individual that's been around a prospect
for a year.
For more than a year.
What is that prospect like on an
everyday basis? How are they wired? That
along with the tape I think gives you
the best chance to shrink the margin for
error. Philosophically as a first-year
head coach do you need 6, 24, 37 for
that matter to be immediate impact
players? Are you Are you willing to say,
"You know what? I That guy might take a
little bit of time even at 6 or at 24,
but I love his long-term potential.
Let's do it."
I hope they all are. Hope every draft
pick is immediate impact. It's more fun
that way. Um
there are some really good players in
this draft that I am
confident that all the way down to 39
that there's going to be an impact
player. You have spoken repeatedly about
how you would like this quarterback
competition to look, but you also said
that at Georgia you had a situation once
four or five quarterbacks. That just
doesn't work. You said, "I think that's
not ideal." What is the ideal
quarterback competition look for you
starting as early as April 7th?
Well, first of all, I think we've got
three outstanding quarterbacks that are
going to be competing uh for a starting
position. Like any any position on our
team there's going to be competition.
So, I'm excited to get started with
those guys. I don't think as I said this
morning, I don't think you can give
equal reps to all in a given day.
Explain that. Well, in a given day I
don't think in any position you can't
you can't go into a day and say
everybody's going to get equal reps.
Cuz everybody's not equal in terms of
where they are in terms of on our team.
Now, every position's a little bit
different. Uh certainly you have
starters that have shown on tape
their ability to play at a high level.
Well, they're going to start with our
ones. Mhm. Then you You're going to have
to have some form of a depth chart the
first day that you roll out there,
right? That you're able to go against
each other. You're going to have to
okay, here's the ones. Okay, well, who
is that? Well, there's some some
guesswork involved and yet there's some
of it that that that's proven already on
film. Can somebody win that job before
the third week of July?
Sure, they can.
Or they can at least put themselves in
position
to go into the fall as our starter. No
matter what position.
>> that come July training camp.
>> Exactly. To at least take a step forward
in terms of where we believe they're at
at that moment.
>> Ideally would that be the best case
scenario
>> Of course. Okay. Shoulders, horse head,
have you named it? I have not. I have
not named it yet. Okay.
Um but it's it's [laughter]
>> Should I? I don't know.
It it Have you Has he seen Godfather?
Like I'm the horse head's in on here.
>> but it it's it's not a bloodied real
head.
>> it wasn't in your building. I understood
that.
>> Right. I understand that. I wasn't
suggesting. It was just I haven't heard
of anyone giving anyone a horse head
before. Yeah.
I think there's been players before that
might have sent one that or wanted to
send one that's a threat, but I don't
think that was the case.
>> Are you open to gifts? I am open to
gifts. I think it was great. I was not
expecting that from him. I do not expect
it. Do not send gifts. That is not I I
found it
I I found it interesting. Okay. And I
was excited.
>> Yeah.
>> Who doesn't like presents? Two quick
questions. Uh Deshaun Watson in 2023.
You had a front row seat. You were there
in Baltimore when he had that perfect
second half. David Njoku's breaking
tackles. Dustin Hopkins is sitting a
field goal.
You saw that firsthand.
Is that guy still in there? And if so,
how do you get that guy? God, I hope so.
Uh when I did get a chance chance to
meet with him uh
it was refreshing. And I think he's
excited to get started. Another
opportunity
uh with a new staff and uh I can't wait
to get started again come come April
7th.
And finally, you texted with Miles. What
was that text convo like? Were there
emojis? Were there No, there's no no
emojis. It was just I was I was asking
him a couple of questions. I had some
insight. At that time he happened to be
overseas. Well, at first he was
traveling, then he was overseas for the
Olympics, but I look forward to to
getting him back in the building getting
started.
>> All right. And a good conversation. Yep.
No question. April 7th, we'll see you
there. Thanks for doing this.
>> Fantastic. Thank you.
>> haircut. Well done. Thank you. It's good
stuff there with Todd Monken. My first
chance to interview him one-on-one.
Certainly was there give a at the
combine and we made some uh small talk
there when he was on CBD. I really like
the guy. I think Browns fans are going
to like him as well. He he Listen, he's
going to be diplomatic when he has to be
diplomatic. He's an NFL head coach and
every word that anyone says on the
podium or into a microphone is going to
be over analyzed, but he's going to be
fairly direct and that was the
impression we got from Jimmy Haslam,
from from Dee Haslam, from everybody
here is that you're going to know where
you stand with Todd Monken, period. And
the players are going to know that
starting next week. Players are in the
building give a next week. We'll hear
from the coach again and the off-season
program gets rolling on April 7th. Like
the off-season's over, buddy.
No. No. No. No. No. And by the way, like
I know there was a lot of conversation
about the haircut. I am happy to take
care of your haircut, Todd. Like I got
you.
>> You get you.
>> Like make it make it simple.
Low maintenance. At unlike Siciliano
real simple. Like was it Eddie Murphy
in Coming to America? Just make it nice
and neat. That's right. [laughter]
That's right. That's it. That's all you
got to do. All right. So, the off-season
program it gets rolling with there's
going to be the the voluntary mini camp
on the week of the draft, which is
something very new. Um at least
obviously I I don't remember that under
Kevin. I wasn't around in 2020. It was
also the COVID year in 2020 obviously.
So, so things were a bit different.
Um and also we find out this week.
It's not official official, but it is
out there. It looks as if the Browns are
going to be doing a joint practice in
Cleveland
with your Buffalo Bills.
Uh I'm good with that. The last time we
did joint practices with the Bills
uh John Paul Football was on our team.
We chartered an Amtrak train to
Rochester, New York. We didn't fly. Oh,
yeah. We took an Amtrak train for joint
practices with the Bills up in There was
a
uh St. John Fisher College, I believe,
is the name of it. Just outside of
Rochester.
The only memorable part that I like to
keep in mind uh would be the nighttime
events because the practices did not go
well. Let's just put it that way. Uh we
don't know the dates yet uh for that
Bills
uh joint practice. However, it should be
noted that the Foo Fighters and I I'm
going to be there with bells on
uh when Dave Grohl comes to town. The
Foo Fighters are playing Huntington Bank
Field on the 10th. It's a Monday night
of August. The Hall of Fame game is the
6th. That is the first full week. No,
the the Hall of Fame game is the 31st.
Is it the first or the No, the 6th.
Either way, don't know yet when the
Buffalo Bills give a will be here uh for
the Josh Allen-Miles Garrett reunion
from last year. But when we get that
preseason schedule, we will get it to
you. Looks like one
road game, two home games in the
preseason. That's not set in stone, but
that's certainly what it appears like
because generally it goes cyclically and
last year we were on the road. It goes
back and forth for those two preseason
games in Carolina and in Philadelphia.
Rules changes very quickly. The big
headline here is that the NFL has voted
in voted in
if there is a work stoppage with the
officials, the ability to use replay
assist to correct calls and to help
guide the replacement officials if it
comes to that. Give me your thoughts.
All right.
Let's see what happens, but I I think I
like this on a bigger stage even when
the main officials are there.
I I can't argue with something like
this. I I'm fascinated to see how it
comes about. I'm a little more concerned
that we're spending a lot of time
talking about replacement officials like
Yeah.
>> trending that it's going to happen more
so than not happen, I feel.
>> We're a long way from the first game.
However, we are not a long way from
officials showing up at training camp
and helping teams and obviously going
through that whole cycle. So, they're
going to need officials soon. Obviously,
we're a long way however from week one.
Real quick here, the other thing that
was changed when it comes to replay
assist is this. So, this goes into
effect regardless whether or not we have
replacement officials is that the league
and replay assist now has the ability to
kick a player out and and that's the key
change here, drop a flag if there is a
non-football act that needs an ejection.
There were two plays the league says
last year. One of them the Josh Shaw
play obviously in the Super Bowl in
which players should have been ejected
on the field for a punch thrown or
a a non-football act and it was missed.
But it was clear and obvious that was a
punch. That's an ejection and it was
missed. The league now with replay
assist has the ability to stop the game
and kick that player out. And from what
I understand is there wasn't a lot of
pushback. People think this is the right
way to handle it. What was added is that
when Kevin O'Connell and Sean Payton
among others stood up in the meeting and
said, "Wait a minute. If we are going to
kick somebody out, there's got to be a
flag as well. You can't have it third
and 10. It's an incompletion and then
after on replay you realize that wide
receiver threw a punch, that guy should
be ejected and then make it fourth and
10. No, at point it should be the
defensive team have the option of making
that third and 25 or You know what I'm
saying? You should be able You need to
be able to throw the flag and apply the
penalty yardage as well.
Yeah, absolutely. And there was no pu-
There wasn't a lot of pushback there.
>> I'm assuming the other play was the DK
Metcalf play or the the DK Metcalf It
It might have been No one raised their
hand and asked Okay.
>> which one it was in the presser um when
Rich McKay, the co-chair of the
competition committee, was up there. But
that is that is fair to assume. We are
recording this before Roger Goodell's
press conference to end the annual
meeting and the fleet of black SUVs to
head back to Phoenix Sky Harbor Airport
and people get the heck out of here. But
that is imminent. Don't know if there's
going to be any major news out of that.
Certainly, I can't imagine major news
that affects your Browns. So, with that
we will tell you that we are excited to
get the off-season program rolling next
week in another edition of Best Podcast
Available brought to you by the Bullseye
Event Group. For award-winning game day
experiences, visit
bullseyeeventgroup.com.
Gibeault, any final thoughts?
Happy Easter, my friend. Have a good
holiday back home with the fam.
Everybody be safe. Have a good holiday.
And we'll be back with you next week
from the CrossCountry Mortgage Campus
with players in the building. The salad
bar is back in the cafe. Let's go.
Buddy, save me a line. Save me a spot at
the salad bar.